https://www.shape5.com/privacy_policy.html

Forum Support - Old
Pre-Sales Questions?
Custom Services
Contact
Demo
Get More With A Membership
At Shape5 we are dedicated to saving you money! We sell memberships instead of individual products. With a membership you can download any or all products in a club, as many times as you want, all for the same price that most companies charge for just one single product! This means if you decide to change to different design later, you can do this without having to purchase a brand new design every time.
What if you could setup four websites for only $22 each? That is cheaper than most developers charge for a single theme or template. Our Best Value Membership does just this! For just $89 you can configure up to four sites using our designs, which equals to an incredibly low price of only $22 per website!
Note - A membership is not a subscription service. All products work as normal once your membership expires, and there are no automatic renewals.
Choose A Membership
Shape 5 LLC respects the privacy of its users whether they use our website located at www.shape5.com to purchase licenses to website templates, extensions, and other related software, utilize related services offered from time to time, or simply view the website. The following privacy policy is designed to inform you, as a user of this website, about the types of information that we may gather or collect from you in connection with your use of our website. It also is intended to explain the conditions under which Shape5 LLC uses and discloses that information, and your rights in relation to that information. Each time you use our website, the current version of this privacy policy will apply.
BY USING OR ACCESSING THE WEBSITE, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRACTICES DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.
Children
The Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. Shape5 LLC does not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13.
What Information Do We Collect?
At the time of registration a user will need to submit the following information: full name, email address, a valid password, registration date, last visit date, purchase history, and IP address. Shape5 LLC is not involved in any way of the collection of this data, it is submitted solely by the user. No other information is required or collected at the time of registration or any at any other time or process of our website. This information is used to personalize a user's experience on our website and for occasional communication. This information is stored on an encrypted web server, and is not shared with any outside party with the exception of email addresses for newsletter correspondence (see Shared Information). This information is used to enable us to provide service to our customers, and maintain the security of their accounts.
Shared Information
Shape5 LLC does not share any user related information with any third party companies except for email addresses which are used solely for newsletter correspondence, which the user agrees to at the time of registration. Email addresses will be imported/exported using constantcontact.com, a mass emailing website, to use as acommunication tool with our members.
Financial Information
Any financial information such as credit card numbers are kept with our third-party payment processors: 2checkout and PayPal. Shape5 LLC does not store or request any financial information for any reason.
Support Communications
The support staff of Shape5 LLC may from time to time request access to a member's website to assist in debugging a product within their specified hosting environment or to make necessary modifications for the user. This may be done via email or through our support forums. Requests may include admin logins, ftp access, cpanel access, or general logins pertaining to the problem at hand. Only moderators of Shape5 LLC are authorized to ask for such information, the moderators of Shape5 LLC are: mikek, jonahh, mnicoll, and trineer. Any information requested by moderators is kept secure and confidential between just the moderator and the member themselves. Requested information is never shared with anyone but the moderator.
General Company Communications
All communication with Shape5 LLC and its customers is done via our website forum or via email. Phone support is not offered.
Security
We take security of your information, such as name and email address, very seriously and use reasonable electronic, personnel, and physical measures to protect it from loss, theft, alteration, or misuse. We work to protect your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the information that you provide online at our Web Site
Google Analytics
We do utilize Google Analytics on our website, as part of doing business. We use information gathered by Google Analytics to better understand our customers' needs and to detect any issues users are having with our websites.
Right of Removal
If you would like to request to have your personal information removed from our servers, you may do so by submitting a request via our Contact Page.
All requests will be addressed within the time frame required under GDPR policies. Keep in mind that removing your data is permanent and will result in the cancellation of any currently-active services without refund, as well as any Member Bonuses.
Web Cookies
A Web Cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a user's computer, and that the user's browser provides to the website each time the user submits a query to the site. Shape5 LLC's website will store cookies on user's machines to track membership durations, active logins and forum access. No personal information is recorded or collected at this time, it is simply used for normal membership processes of the website.
Terms of Use
Please also take the time to review our Terms of Use page found here.
Our Latest Releases
Read More
Comments
Buy Now
Demo
Read More
Comments
Buy Now
Demo
Looking for the largest variety in template designs? Look no more.
Never buy 1 theme again. Signups start at just $89 for access to all of our themes.
Join Now
Our Products
Best Joomla Templates
Free Joomla Templates
Best Joomla Extensions
Free Joomla Extensions
WordPress Themes
Free WordPress Themes
Join Our Newsletter
Stay up to date with sales, promotions and new product releases.
© 2020 Shape5.com Professional Joomla Templates, and WordPress Themes
Send Us An Email
Please send us your questions and we will email you back as soon as we can. Product support questions should be posted in our support forums under the Help menu. Our staff will assist you from there.
Your Message...
Send Message
